{
    "id": "ef0b053b005e4583904882ca56e6e2eb",
    "title": "Continuous And Non-continuous Verbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. doubtful about the new plan.",
            "description": "When feel means have an opinion, it is not used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50e72868c5384c29b5c1f41aaf6d70a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… this scenery.",
            "description": "The verb love is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "am loving",
                "love",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad1318de78894c9ba46e5a75a1d5e23e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. fine.",
            "description": "To talk about feelings that are going on, we can use the simple and continuous forms of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "830218a7bd734d09a3001ed24bf8ff43"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… your mother tomorrow.",
            "description": "See has a continuous form when it is used to talk about a pre-planned future event. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aab52a0903724b6ba2e8abc8837981b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… you have a problem with me.",
            "description": "When see means understand it is not used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "749d18c5fbc14efb9d48e93497eb81ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "That creature …………………………. like a rabbit.",
            "description": "When look means seem, it is not used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "looks",
                "is looking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ffcc2856672e4bba83f11226c6d22281"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… that you are quitting your job.",
            "description": "The word hear is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "am hearing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cebf408a9a8d410395669c8a0829c2eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… of writing a novel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "think",
                "am thinking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6100f4002c664cc288e1ca0e235df619"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. we should not do it.",
            "description": "When think means have an opinion, it is not used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "think",
                "am thinking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "696c3cf1ea02412c8f5f22f89daaf68b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… with the argument that education should be free for all.",
            "description": "The verb agree is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "agree",
                "am agreeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef56c0c50b604067b959e5abb5bfdcef"
        },
        {
            "question": "We may or may not go. It …………………………. on the weather.",
            "description": "The verb depend is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "is depending",
                "depends",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a8052bad2ef4930851844b7dd2c959a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I still ………………………… meeting the seer.",
            "description": "Remember is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "am remembering",
                "remember",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c5dd0c55b0f4f1597b00fc63ad75963"
        }
    ]
}